Previously on the show. Slowy fell sick.
ความเดิมตอนที่แล้ว สโลวี่ไม่สบาย
The stars initially thought that Wolffy and the goats made him sick.
ตอนแรกพวกดวงดาวคิดว่า วูฟฟี่และพวกแกะทำให้เบบี๋ป่วย
The goats insisted on helping, which finally got Slowy better.
พวกแกะยืนยันว่ายังไงก็จะช่วย สุดท้ายแล้วสโลวี่ก็อาการดีขึ้น
The stars have also come to accept Wolffy and the goats.
และในที่สุดพวกดวงดาว ก็ยอมรับวูฟฟี่และพวกแกะ
But how can they make Slowy go back to the way he used to be?
แต่พวกเขาจะทำให้สโลวี่ กลับไปเป็นเหมือนเดิมได้อย่างไร
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Invincible Baby"
"แกะน้อยสุดกวนกับหมาป่าจอมป่วน ตอน เบบี๋นี่สุดยอดไร้เทียมทานจริงๆ นะ"
So you ate the fruit from the tree and became small?
หัวหน้ากินผลไม้จากต้นไม้แล้วก็ตัวเล็กลงเหรอ
Those are infantilising fruits.
พวกนั้นคือผลไม้กลายสภาพเป็นเบบี๋
They make people young again.
ผลไม้นั่นจะทำให้เราเป็นหนุ่มสาวอีกครั้ง
Baby, it's time to eat.
เบบี๋ ได้เวลากินนมแล้วนะ
I made something delicious for you.
ฉันชงนมอร่อยๆ มาให้หนูด้วยนะ
I can't drink from a milk bottle in front of the children. That's too embarrassing.
ฉันดื่มนมจากขวดต่อหน้าเด็กๆ ไม่ได้หรอก แบบนั้นน่าอายจะตายไป
Grandpa Elder. The chief is actually an adult, not a baby.
คุณปู่ดาวผู้เฒ่า จริงๆ แล้วหัวหน้าเป็นผู้ใหญ่ไม่ใช่เบบี๋
He became a baby after eating one of those infantilizing fruits.
เขากลายเป็นเบบี๋ เพราะกินผลไม้กลายสภาพเป็นเบบี๋
You keep saying he's an adult. How old is he?
นายเอาแต่พูดว่าเขาเป็นผู้ใหญ่ เขาอายุเท่าไหร่กันแน่เนี่ย
He's in his 80s.
เขาอายุ 80 กว่าแล้วฮะ
That's still very young. I'm more than 2,000 years old.
ก็ยังอายุน้อยอยู่นะ ฉันอายุมากกว่า 2,000 ปีแล้วล่ะ
Come, drink some milk.
มามะ ดื่มนมซะนะ
How can we turn Chief back to what he used to be?
เราจะคืนร่างเดิมให้หัวหน้าได้ยังไงนะ
You can look for Time Star.
นายลองตามหา "ดาวกาลเวลา" ดูก็ได้นะ
Who is that?
ใครเหรอฮะ
He's the most famous performance judge in the sky.
เขาคือผู้ตัดสินการแสดงชื่อดังบนท้องฟ้า
If he gives a performance five stars, everyone will eagerly come to see it.
ถ้าเขาตัดสินว่าการแสดงไหนได้ห้าดาว ทุกคนก็จะแห่มาดูกันเลยล่ะ
But what does that have to do with Chief?
แต่มันเกี่ยวอะไรกับหัวหน้าล่ะคะ
That's because his superpower is to make people old.
ก็พลังวิเศษของเขาทำให้เราแก่ลงได้ไงล่ะ
How can we find him?
เราจะตามหาเขาได้ยังไงฮะ
He's always alone. It's hard to find him.
เขามักอยู่ตามลำพัง ยากที่จะตามตัวเจอ
But...
แต่ว่า...
But what?
แต่อะไรฮะ
If our troupe manages to get 10,000 likes,
ถ้ากองทัพเราแสดงจนได้ 10,000 ไลก์
he'll definitely come.
เขาก็จะมาอย่างแน่นอน
Great! What does he look like?
เยี่ยมเลย! เขาหน้าตาเป็นยังไงฮะ
Um, I think there's a photo of him in Handsome Star's place.
ฉันคิดว่าในHandsome Star's place มีรูปเขาอยู่นะ
Who's that? Can he make me handsome?
เขาเป็นใครฮะ ทำให้ผมหล่อได้ไหม
No.
ไม่ได้
That's because his superpower is to make himself handsome when no one's around.
นั่นเพราะพลังวิเศษของเขาทำให้ตัวเองหล่อ เมื่ออยู่ตามลำพังได้เท่านั้น
What can I do to those stars so I can catch Slowy?
ฉันต้องทำยังไงกับพวกดวงดาวนั่นนะ ถึงจะจับตัวสโลวี่มาได้
Pay.
จ่ายเงินสิ
That's too simple.
แบบนั้นมันง่ายไป
I'm asking you to pay now!
ฉันบอกให้จ่ายมาเดี๋ยวนี้ไงล่ะ!
Okay.
ได้เลยจ้ะ
Go next door and get me some facial masks. I'm going to buy shoes.
ไปห้องข้างๆ ซื้อมาส์กหน้ามาให้หน่อยค่ะ ฉันจะไปซื้อรองเท้าต่อนะ
Okay.
ได้เลยจ้ะ
There are so many people buying masks.
มีคนซื้อมาส์กหน้าเยอะจังเลย
Grandpa.
คุณปู่
Who did you call grandpa?
นายเรียกใครว่าคุณปู่
Have you ever seen such a fit grandpa?
นายเคยเห็นคุณปู่ที่ฟิตปั๋งอย่างนี้รึไง
Are you not a grandpa?
คุณไม่ใช่คุณปู่เหรอ
Then what are you doing at the senior activity center?
ถ้างั้นคุณมาทำอะไรที่ศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุล่ะ
What? Senior activity center?
อะไรนะ ศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุอะไรเหรอ
Oh, dear. I came to the wrong place.
แย่ล่ะสิ ฉันมาผิดที่เหรอเนี่ย
Senior activity center?
ศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุเหรอ
So old people love senior activity centers.
งั้นคนแก่ก็ชอบศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุสินะ
What if I open one?
ถ้าฉันเปิดศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุเองล่ะ
The stars will be at the center all the time.
พวกดวงดาวก็จะอยู่ที่ศูนย์นี้ตลอดเวลา
Then I'll have lots of time to get the goats.
ฉันก็จะมีเวลาเหลือเฟือออกไปจับพวกแกะ
That's a great idea.
ไอเดียนั่นเยี่ยมเลยนะ
Where are my masks?
ไหนล่ะมาส์กหน้าของฉัน
How handsome you are.
ตัวเรานี่หล่อจริงๆ เลย
Grandpa Handsome Star.
คุณปู่ดาวหล่อเป๊ะเวอร์
Who's that?
นั่นใครน่ะ
Sorry to disturb you, Grandpa Handsome Star.
ขอโทษที่รบกวนฮะ คุณปู่ดาวหล่อเป๊ะเวอร์
We need your help.
เราอยากให้คุณปู่ช่วยหน่อยฮะ
This is the photo of Time Star. Here you go.
นี่คือรูปของดาวกาลเวลา
Handsome Star, let's go out and have some fun.
ดาวหล่อเป๊ะเวอร์ออกไปสนุกกันเถอะ!
The picture of grandpa Time Star flew away.
รูปคุณปู่ดาวกาลเวลาปลิวไปแล้ว
Thank you.
ขอบคุณนะ
Today is the official opening of Wolffy's senior activity center!
วันนี้คือวันเปิด "ศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุวูฟฟี่" อย่างเป็นทางการ
Come. Come inside.
เชิญเข้าไปด้านในเลย
Dear friends,
เพื่อนๆ ที่รักทั้งหลาย
this is Wolffy's senior activity center.
นี่คือ "ศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุวูฟฟี่"
Look at the layout.
ดูแผนผังของศูนย์นี้สิ
Look at the facilities. It's so...
ดูเครื่องอำนวยความสะดวกสิ มันช่าง...
Isn't it amazing?
วิเศษไปเลยใช่ไหมล่ะ
It's mediocre.
มันก็ธรรมดาๆ แหละ
But since you just opened, we'll come to visit.
แต่ในเมื่อนายเพิ่งเปิดศูนย์ เราก็เลยแวะมาน่ะ
Thank you.
ขอบคุณนะ
I need to think of a way to get Slowy.
ฉันต้องคิดหาวิธีจับตัวสโลวี่มาให้ได้เลย
By the way, is the baby still feeling unwell?
ว่าแต่เบบี๋ยังไม่สบายอยู่รึเปล่า
Shall I give him a check-up?
จะให้ฉันลองตรวจดูไหมล่ะ
Well...
คือ...
We don't want him to get sick again.
เราไม่อยากให้เบบี๋ป่วยอีกนะ
I'll let you have him then.
งั้นฉันให้นายอุ้มเบบี๋ไปก็ได้
Sure.
ได้เลย
The little goat has a mark. You must have one too.
เจ้าแกะตัวน้อยมีปานเวทย์ นายก็ต้องมีด้วยเหมือนกัน
There it is.
นั่นไงล่ะ
Is the baby okay?
เบบี๋โอเคไหม
I haven't examined him yet.
ฉันยังไม่ได้ตรวจเบบี๋เลย
Oh.
อ๋อเหรอ
I'm not used to having someone looking when I'm examining people.
ฉันไม่ชินกับการที่มีใครมายืนดูตอนตรวจน่ะ
It's okay, I'm not looking at you.
ไม่เป็นไรหรอก ฉันไม่ดูนายซะหน่อย
I'm looking at the baby.
ฉันกำลังดูเบบี๋อยู่ต่างหากล่ะ
But you will distract me.
แต่นายทำให้ฉันไม่มีสมาธินะ
I'll leave then.
งั้นฉันไปก็ได้
Is the baby okay?
เบบี๋โอเคไหม
He's okay.
เบบี๋โอเค ไม่เป็นไรหรอก
If he's okay, I'll take him then.
ถ้าเบบี๋โอเคแล้ว งั้นฉันอุ้มไปเลยนะ
No. He's not okay.
ไม่สิ เบบี๋ไม่โอเคเลยล่ะ
What did you say?
นายพูดว่าอะไรนะ
I'm sorry.
ฉันขอโทษที
When I get anxious, my superpower gets out of control.
ถ้าฉันกังวลใจล่ะก็ ฉันจะควบคุมพลังวิเศษไม่ได้
What's wrong with the baby?
เบบี๋เป็นอะไรไปเหรอ
I mean, he needs some rest.
เบบี๋ต้องการพักผ่อนน่ะ
Stop holding him everywhere you go.
เลิกอุ้มเบบี๋ไปไหนต่อไหนด้วยได้แล้ว
What should I do with my hair?
นี่ฉันจะทำยังไงกับผมดีล่ะเนี่ย
Let me help you. Shorter hair!
มาให้ฉันช่วยนายเอง ผมจงสั้นลง!
My hair!
ผมของฉัน!
Why do you guys keep coming over?
ทำไมพวกนายต้องมาป้วนเปี้ยนอยู่เรื่อยเลย
I was afraid the baby might be bored when he wakes up.
ฉันกลัวว่าเบบี๋ตื่นแล้วจะเหงาน่ะสิ
I'll be there when he wakes up. Just go and have fun.
ฉันจะอยู่ด้วยตอนเบบี๋ตื่นก็แล้วกัน พวกนายไปสนุกกันเถอะ
All right.
ก็ได้
Let me help you!
มาให้ฉันช่วยนายเอง!
Sorry. My aura is just too strong.
โทษทีนะ แสงออร่าของฉันมันแจ่มเกินไปหน่อย
The photo is dirty now.
รูปเลอะเทอะหมดเลย
I'm sorry.
โทษทีนะ
If I hadn't asked Handsome Star to go to Wolffy's senior activity center,
ถ้าฉันไม่ขอร้องให้ดาวหล่อเป๊ะเวอร์ ไปศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุวูฟฟี่ล่ะก็
the photo wouldn't have flown away and it wouldn't have gotten dirty.
รูปก็คงไม่ปลิวออกมาและเลอะเทอะแบบนี้
Wolffy has a senior activity center?
วูฟฟี่มีศูนย์ผู้สูงอายุด้วยเหรอคะ
Yes. Elder Star and the baby are there now.
ใช่ ตอนนี้ดาวผู้เฒ่าแเละเบบี๋ก็อยู่ที่นั่น
You old goat.
เจ้าแกะเฒ่าเอ๊ย
Stop struggling.
เลิกดิ้นได้แล้ว
Ah!
อ๊าก!
Don't run!
อย่าหนีนะ!
The baby won!
เบบี๋ชนะแล้ว!
Help!
ช่วยด้วย!
The baby is amazing.
เบบี๋นี่ช่างมหัศจรรย์จริงๆ
Seeing you play makes me want to play badminton too.
เห็นเบบี๋เล่นแล้ว ทำให้ฉันก็อยากเล่นแบดมินตันด้วย
Me too. Baby, be good.
ฉันก็เหมือนกัน เบบี๋เป็นเด็กดีนะ
Play with Uncle Wolffy.
เล่นกับลุงวูฟฟี่ไปก่อนนะ
Yes, give him to me.
ใช่เลย ส่งเบบี๋มาให้ฉัน
I won't let you off.
ฉันไม่ปล่อยให้นายหนีไปได้แน่
Help!
ช่วยด้วย!
Baby, hush now, or I'll lose.
เบบี๋เงียบๆ นะ เดี๋ยวฉันก็แพ้กันพอดี
Come on, baby. Play with me over here. Don't get in their way.
มาสิเบบี๋ มาเล่นกับฉันตรงนี้ดีกว่า อย่าไปยุ่งพวกเขาเลยนะ
Yes. This'll make me win.
ใช่ เล่นแบบนี้ฉันชนะแน่
Baby, you're awesome.
เบบี๋นี่สุดยอดไปเลย
Baby, can you play chess?
เบบี๋ เล่นหมากรุกเป็นเหรอ
He can play badminton too.
เบบี๋เล่นแบดมินตันเป็นด้วยนะ
That's not all. He got a perfect score bowling.
ไม่ใช่แค่นั้นนะ เบบี๋เล่นโบว์ลิ่งได้คะแนนสุดยอดเลยล่ะ
Wow! You're really an invincible baby.
ว้าว เบบี๋นี่สุดยอดไร้เทียมทานจริงๆ นะ
All of you guys underestimate me. Ah!
พวกนายดูถูกฉันมากไปแล้วนะ!
I thought I saw something fly out.
ฉันคิดว่าเห็นอะไรลอยออกไปนะ
Chief is all right! That's great.
หัวหน้าไม่เป็นไรแล้ว! เยี่ยมไปเลย!
We just need to clean the photo.
เราก็แค่ทำความสะอาดรูปนี้ซะหน่อย
Chief. We'll find Time Star and get you back to normal.
หัวหน้า เราจะตามหาดาวกาลเวลาให้เจอ จะได้คืนร่างเดิมให้หัวหน้าได้สักทีนะ
I guess Chief is going to have to drink milk again.
สงสัยหัวหน้าคงต้องดื่มนมอีกแล้ว
Baby, we really underestimated you.
เบบี๋ เราประเมินความสามารถของหนูต่ำไป
You're amazing.
หนูน่ะสุดยอดมากเลยนะ
My heart tells me I want to play chess.
หัวใจฉันร่ำร้องว่าอยากเล่นหมากรุก
Come play with me.
มาเล่นกับฉันสิ
Uh, uh.
โอ๊ะโอ...
I'll do anything to avoid drinking milk.
ฉันยอมทำทุกอย่างเพื่อจะได้ไม่ต้องดื่มนม
But before that, you have to drink your milk.
แตก่อนจะเล่นหนูต้องดื่มนมก่อนนะ